U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations on Microfilm 5398 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations on Microfilm
1912-1915
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations
5398 mf
2 cubic feet
18 microfilm reels
Records (documents), microfilm.
Microfilm copy of the reports in the Library of the Wisconsin State Historical Society and the Shelf list of the Reports of the Commission.
5622653
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 07, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Commission on Industrial Relations was a commission created by the U.S. Congress on August 23, 1912. The commission studied work conditions throughout the industrial United States between 1913 and 1915.
Scope and Contents
Microfilm copy of the reports in the Library of the Wisconsin State Historical Society and the Shelf list of the Reports of the Commission.
Reports of the Commission and reports of investigations made for the Commission.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Industrial relations -- United States; Labor violence. United States.; United States. Commission on Industrial Relations.
5622653
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. And reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 101)
  Scope and Contents
  positive --
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. And reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 102)
  positive
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. And reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 103)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. And reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 104)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. And reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 105)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. And reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 106)
- Record Group E-13: U.S. commission on Industrial Relations 1912-1915 Reports, Reel #7 (Reel 107)
- Record Group E-13: U.S. commission on Industrial Relations 1912-1915 Reports, Reel #8 (Reel 108)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. & reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 109)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. & reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 110)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. & reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 111)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. & reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 112)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. & reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 113)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. & reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 114)
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912-1915: Reports of the Comm. & reports of investigations made for the commission (Reel 115)